freshpromotions.com.au 2009-10-09

# Privacy Policy - Promotional Products, Promotional Items, Corporate Gifts - Fresh Promotions Australia

|   
---  
|  |  01 Oct 09  
**Promotional Drink Coolers**  
It's been the hottest September on record and naturally promotional products buyers' thoughts turn to insulated drink coolers. The range of promotiona...  
---  
|  read more  
19 Sep 09  
**Fresh Number 418**  
Alexa, the international internet traffic and web ranking authority has listed Fresh Promotions as the 418th most popular site in Australia....  
|  read more  
14 Sep 09  
**Christmas Promo Gifts**  
With the Christmas corporate gifts giving season upon us now if the time to start planning for your purchase of end of year promotional gifts...  
|  read more  
03 Sep 09  
**Printed Hanes T Shirts**  
The classic American T shirts have arrived! Screen printed Hanes promotional t shirts are made of the finest quality, 100% American cotton and are now...  
|  read more  
30 Aug 09  
**Christmas Promotional Products**  
It's already started, major companies organising their branded promotional products for the Christmas corporate gift giving season. As always the best...  
|  read more  
|  |   
| 

**Fresh Promotions and Fresh Promotional Network Privacy Statement**

Fresh Promotions has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This policy describes our practices regarding personal information collected through our website or through any other means.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time; the effective date noted below will indicate the date the policy was last updated. Please visit our website periodically to review any changes.

**What Information do We Collect from You?**  
All information you provide will be kept confidential and is used to support our business relationship and the service we provide. This website uses an order inquiry form to allow you to request information, products, and services. We collect your contact information (such as your e-mail address or your company information) to allow us to send samples, orders, information about our products, and promotional materials. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future communication. Just send an email to info@freshpromotions.com.au to make this request.

**Personal Information Disclosure**  
Fresh Promotions will not give or sell any information you provided to any third parties under any circumstances for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. The information protected includes any information about you, your order, and your purchase history. Your information may be shared with contractors of Fresh Promotions for the purpose of performing services for Fresh Promotions related only to your order or sample request. Fresh Promotions may release personal identifiable information when required to by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a legal process.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
When you opt-in to receive communications from Fresh Promotions, you will receive information we believe will be of use and interest to you. For example:

We keep you informed about the latest deals, new service, sell-out specials, etc. that we think you will find valuable.

We may update you on any important changes to our website.

If you choose to opt out of our communication, you may do so in the following ways:

**You may e-mail your request to:**  

**You may send mail to the following postal address:**  
Fresh Promotions Pty. Ltd.  
PO Box 1516  
Fortitude Valley Qld 4006

**You may fax in your request:**  
Fax No: 07 3254 1939

**You may call to make your request:**  
Toll Free: 1800 129 999

Privacy Policy Last Modified 7th February 2007
